[
    {
        "question": "Kass",
        "answer": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Koer",
        "answer": "Dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lehm",
        "answer": "Cow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kärbes",
        "answer": "Fly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Laud",
        "answer": "Table"
    },
    {
        "question": "Haamer",
        "answer": "Hammer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Küsimus",
        "answer": "Question"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vastus",
        "answer": "Answer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Taim",
        "answer": "Plant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Klaas",
        "answer": "Glass"
    }
]
